A Finding Aid to the Francis V. O'Connor Papers, 1920-2009, in the Archives of American Art AAA.oconfran
Archives of American Art
- Publications, 1939-1985; Series 2; 4.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-11, BV 25-26, OV 27
  - Federal Support for the Visual Arts: The New Deal and Now, 1939-1985; 2.1
    - Draft, Cover Layout, circa 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Draft, Guide to New Deal Art Project Documentation, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Report, Preliminary Report of Activities and Accomplishments, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Report, Federal Support for the Visual Arts: The New Deal and Now, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - Research, Administrator and Artist Lists, circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Research, Annotated Lists of WPA Reports, circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Research, Classification Key for National Archives Record Groups, circa 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Research, Data, circa 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 13-20)
      Oversized material housed in BV 25-26 and OV 27.
    - Research, Division of Information, circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Research, FAP, circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Research, National Archives, circa 1968 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Research, New York City, circa 1939-1969 (Box 8, Folder 24-26)
    - Research, New York State, circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Research, States (other than New York), circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Research, Welfare/Relief, circa 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - Research, World's Fair, circa 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Research, Notes on File Series "211", circa 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Research, Notes on File Series "651", circa 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Research, Photograph Index List, circa 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Research, Miscellaneous Record Group Notes, circa 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Oversized Computer Printouts from Box 8, Folder 17, circa 1967-1969 (Box BV 25-26)
    - Oversized Coding Forms from Box 8, Folder 18, circa 1967-1969 (Box OV 27)
  - New Deal Art Projects: An Anthology of Memoirs, 1968-1972; 2.2
    Correspondence, book covers, index, and an interview transcript related to the book, New Deal Art Projects, which collects the memoirs of ten artists and administrators who participated in New Deal art projects. The interview transcript is an edited version of the conversation that appears in the book between Audrey McMahon, Olive Gavert, Marchal Landgren, Jacob Kainen, Belisario Contreras, and Francis O'Connor.
    - Correspondence, circa 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
    - Book Cover and Index of Namescirca 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Interview Transcript at End of New Deal Art Projects, circa 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Art for the Millions, 1965-1973; 2.3
    Correspondence, drafts, research notes, and photocopies of research source material related to the book, Art for the Millions. This selection of 103 essays written by WPA/FAP artists was originally solicited by Emanuel Benson for an annual report of the FAP in 1936. The rough manuscript remained unpublished until its rediscovery by O'Connor and subsequent publication in 1973. The book references documentation collected in Series 1.4.
    - Correspondence, American Heritage Publishing Co., Inc., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, New York Graphic Society, circa 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 15-17)
    - Draft Copy, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Draft, Bibliography and Lists, circa 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Draft, Index and Table of Contents, circa 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
    - Draft, Introduction, circa 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Research, Primary Source Documents, 1936-1940, circa 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - Research, Primary Source Document, Book Layout, circa 1939, circa 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Federal Art Patronage Notes, 1971-1985; 2.4
    Administrative printing/subscription records and final print, draft, and editorial copies related to the publication, Federal Art Patronage Notes. This quarterly newsletter was edited and published by O'Connor between 1974 and 1983 and includes articles on the history of federal arts programs, currently sponsored government programs, and recently published academic research on the topic.
    - Administrative, Mailing Lists, circa 1974-1983 (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
    - Administrative, Painting, circa 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
    - Administrative, Stationary Pasteups, circa 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Administrative, Subscription Address File, circa 1974-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
    - Administrative, Subscription Accounts, circa 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 13-17)
    - Administrative, Subscription Correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 10, Folder 18-23)
    - Newsletters, Other Examples, circa 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter, Early Ideas, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Volume 1, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3-6)
    - Volume 2, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7-10)
    - Volume 3, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
    - Volume 4, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14-16)
- New Deal Research Files, 1930-2009; Series 3; 5.6 Linear feet Boxes 11-16
  Materials are of New Deal research collected by or sent to O'Connor in the course of his academic career. These include photocopies of original WPA/FAP correspondence and reports; biographical material on WPA administrators; printed material and notes on scholarly conferences and symposia; final reports on the WPA/FAP; drafts and final copies of academic research by fellow scholars; and printed material on WPA/FAP state specific projects. The events subseries also contains a symposium panel discussion on 1 sound cassette.
  The series is arranged as 6 subseries. Materials for administrators, scholars, and states are arranged alphabetically by name. Events and reports are arranged chronologically, and research is arranged by document type.
  3.1: Administrators, 1940-2009
  3.2: Events, 1935-1986
  3.3: Reports, 1969
  3.4: Scholars, 1967-2002
  3.5: States, 1940-1987
  3.6: WPA/FAP Research, 1930-1997
  - Administrators, 1940-2009; 3.1
    Materials include biographical sketches, curriculum vitae, and photographs documenting the careers of WPA/FAP administrative staff. The subseries also includes original drafts of essays written by Rosalind Browne, Robert Cronbach, Olive Gavert, Jacob Kainen, Marchal Landgren, Audrey McMahon, Lincoln Rothschild, and Joseph Solman, which were gathered by O'Connor for publication in New Deal Art Projects: An Anthology of Memoirs.
    - Baker, Mildred, circa 1967-1999 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Browne, Rosalind, circa 1968-1989 (Box 11, Folder 18-20)
    - Bruce, Edward, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Cahill, Holgar, circa 1965-1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Carr, Sister Eleanor, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Cronbach, Robert, circa 1958-1991 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
    - Dows, Olin, circa 1966-1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Gavert, Olive, circa 1940-1973 (Box 11, Folder 27-29)
    - Kainen, Jacob, circa 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Landgren, Marchal, circa 1940-1979 (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
    - Landgren, Marchal, circa 1940-1970 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - McMahon, Audrey, circa 1965-1989 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
    - Miller, Dorothy, circa 1968-2003 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Rothschild, Lincoln, circa 1940-1973 (Box 12, Folder 8-11)
    - Solman, Joseph, circa 1940-1995 (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
  - Events, 1935-1986; 3.2
    Printed material and notes for seven scholarly New Deal symposia and conferences attended by O'Connor dating from the 1970s to the 1980s. Materials include correspondence, program guides, newsletters, clippings, planning budgets, and drafts of academic papers.
    - Conferences, General Correspondence, circa 1970-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Conference, Glassboro State College, circa 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
    - Conference, 2nd Annual New Deal, circa 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Conference, Columbia University, circa 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
    - Lectures, Louisiana and Carolinas, circa 1972-1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Symposium, University of Connecticut, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Symposium, John Jay College, circa 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - 50th Anniversary Deade, FDR, circa 1935-1985 (Box 12, Folder 23-27)
    - 50th Anniversary Decade, FDR, circa 1982-1983; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Reports, 1969; 3.3
    The subseries consists of three binders of photocopies of original reports drafted by the NY WPA office regarding the Federal Art, Music, Theatre, and Writers Projects, as well as reports on other programs relating to education, exhibitions, and recreation. These comprise weekly and monthly activity records of the four most active WPA arts projects.
    - NY WPA Administration to Washington, D.C. Office, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4-6)
  - Scholars, 1967-2002; 3.4
    General correspondence and draft copies of scholarly essays sent to O'Connor from fellow New Deal researchers, including Penny Liebman's research on Art Front. The subseries also includes three original completed manuscripts: Greta Berman's doctoral dissertation on New Deal murals in New York; Laurance Hurlburt's Mexican Muralists in the United States; and William McDonald's Federal Relief Administration and the Arts.
    - General Correspondence, circa 1967-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7-11)
    - General Correspondence, Media/Film, circa 1985-2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Berman, Greta, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Freeman, Elizabeth, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hall, Daniel, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hurlburt, Laurance, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Liebman, Penny, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Includes editors' list for Art Front.
    - Mathews, Jane de Hart, circa 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - McDonald, William F., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
    - McKinzie, Richard, circa 1967-1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Monroe, Gerald, 1971-1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Rubenstein, Erica Beckh, circa 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - States, 1940-1987; 3.5
    Includes printed material, correspondence, and general information gathered by O'Connor that relate to New Deal arts projects in Arizona, California, Connecticut, Illinois, Maryland, Minnesota, New Mexico, Ohio, Oklahoma, Oregon, Texas, Washington, and Wyoming.
    - Arizona, circa 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - California, circa 1940-1975 (Box 14, Folder 13-16)
    - California, circa 1953-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Illinois, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Maryland, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota, circa 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - New Mexico, 1979-1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Ohio, circa 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Oklahoma, circa 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
    - Oregon, circa 1958-1976 (Box 15, Folder 10-12)
    - Texas, circa 1961-1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Washington, circa 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Wyoming, circa 1946-1975 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - WPA/FAP Research, 1930-1997; 3.6
    Includes miscellaneous printed material on New Deal programs; WPA/FAP lists, reports, and photocopies of original documents; and inventories of collection material held at research institutions.
    - Collections List, New Deal, circa 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Collections List, New Deal Murals, circa 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Institution, Archives of American Art, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Institution, Art Commission of the City of New York, circa 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Institution, College Art Association, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Institution, FDR Library, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Institution, Federal Record Centers, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Institution, General Services Administration, circa 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 23-25)
    - Institution, Library of Congress, circa 1949-1971 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Institution, MoMA, circa 1966 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Institution, National Archives, circa 1946-1967 (Box 15, Folder 28-29)
    - Institution, National Collection of Fine Arts, circa 1969-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, circa 1930-1990 (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
    - Printed Material, Periodicals, 1936-1945 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Printed Material, Miscellaneous, circa 1950-1997 (Box 16, Folder 7-9)
    - WPA/FAP Administration, circa 1938-1965 (Box 16, Folder 10-12)
    - WPA/FAP Allocations, circa 1939-1972 (Box 16, Folder 13-16)
    - WPA/FAP Building Art, circa 1938-1972 (Box 16, Folder 17-19)
    - WPA/FAP Community Art Centers, circa 1937-1965 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - WPA/FAP FERA, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - WPA/FAP PWAP, circa 1933-1971 (Box 16, Folder 22-30)
    - WPA/FAP Section, circa 1935-1975 (Box 16, Folder 31-35)
    - WPA/FAP TRAP, circa 1940-1970 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- New Deal Exhibitions, 1961-1997; Series 4; 1.4 Linear feet Boxes 17-18
  Announcements, catalogs, and supporting press coverage of New Deal art exhibitions in the U.S. gathered by O'Connor from the 1960s to the 1990s. Many of these catalogs provide historical background for the 1943 transfer of art from WPA Federal Art Centers to art institutions across the country. The series includes additional correspondence and planning documentation for the University of Maryland's Decade of Federal Art Patronage (1966), which was curated by O'Connor.
  Materials are arranged chronologically.
  - Smolin Gallery, circa 1961 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Museum of Modern Art, U.S. Government Art Projects, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - University of Maryland, Decade of Federal Art Patronage, circa 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 3-7)
    Curated by Francis O'Connor.
  - YM/YWHA of Essex County, WPA Artists Then and Now, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Smithsonian National Collection of Fine Arts, WPA Prints, circa 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Museum of Art, Art Under the New Deal, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Manhattanville College, WPA Sculpture, 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1972-1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Illinois State Museum, Federal Art Projects of the 1930s, 1973-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Museum of New Mexico, Art in New Mexico, circa 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
    Curated by and includes research from William Spurlock.
  - Washburn Gallery, WPA, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland Public Library, Federal Art in Cleveland, circa 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - de Saisset Art Gallery and Museum, New Deal Art: California, circa 1974-1977 (Box 17, Folder 20-23)
  - Tweed Museum of Art, Minnesota Art Projects in the Depression Years, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Vassar College, 7 American Women, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - de Cordorva Museum, By the People, For the People, circa 1977 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Gallery Association of New York State, New Deal for Art, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 27-28)
  - New York Public Library, WPA Prints, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Newark Museum, Arshile Gorky's Aviation Murals, circa 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Parsons School of Design, New York City WPA Art, circa 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Studio Museum in Harlem, WPA and the Black Artist, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wichita Art Museum, New Deal Art in Kansas, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Hofstra University, New Deal Murals on Long Island, circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Smithsonian National Collection of Fine Arts, Sculpture and the Federal Triangle, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - University of Maryland, History of the Treasury Department Mural Program, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Leigh Yawkey Woodson Art Museum, Wisconsin's New Deal Art, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rutgers University/Newark Museum, New Deal Art: New Jersey, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - University of Arizona, New Deal in the Southwest, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Illinois State Museum, New Deal Art in Illinois; FSA in Illinois, 1983, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - University of Kentucky, New Deal Art, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - ACA Galleries, 50th Anniversary of the AAC, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn Museum, Machine Age in America, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - National Archives Philadelphia, WPA in Philadelphia, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Janet Marqusee Fine Arts, Mural Art in the New Deal Era, 1986-1995 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Smithsonian National Museum of American Art, Murals for the New Deal Era, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Tweed Gallery, WPA Murals in the Health and Hospitals, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Whitney Museum, Constructing American Identity, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Bronx Museum, New Deal for Public Art, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - South Carolina State Museum, New Deal Art in South Carolina, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Parrish Art Museum, State Sponsored Art in te 1930s, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Provincetown Art Association and Museum, WPA Artists, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Project Files, 1965; Series 5; 2 Linear feet Boxes 18-20
  Project files consist of correspondence and supplementary material related to three New Deal research projects O'Connor directed or participated in. These include the CETA (Comprehensive Employment Training Act) projects, a research fellowship at the Smithsonian, and a report on WPA graphic art for the private art collectors Dave and Reba Williams. The Williams research subseries also contains word processing documents on 3 floppy discs.
  The series is arranged as 3 subseries. Materials are arranged by document type.
  5.1: CETA, 1973-1980
  5.2: Smithsonian Fellowship, 1969-1973
  5.3: Williams Collection Research, 1935-1999
  - CETA, 1973-1980; 5.1
    Correspondence, notes, clippings, newsletters, and booklets related to the implementation of federally funded CETA (Comprehensive Employment Training Act) projects. These materials document CETA's administration as well as O'Connor's work as a consultant for projects on both the west and east coasts during the 1970s and 1980s.
    - Correspondence and Background Information, circa 1974-1980 (Box 18, Folder 25--27)
    - Information Packet, circa 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
    - Printed Material, circa 1973-1980 (Box 18, Folder 30-32)
  - Smithsonian Fellowship, 1969-1973; 5.2
    Correspondence, administrative records, and research related to O'Connor's residency as a Smithsonian visiting scholar. The subseries includes a copy of his final report, Register of New Deal Art, National Collection of Fine Arts, as well as original lists, notes, and research generated during the compilation of the report.
    - Administrative, Correspondence, circa 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 33-34)
    - Administrative, Correspondence, circa 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Administrative, Expenses, circa 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Administrative, Office Display, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Art Register Research, Lists, circa 1972-1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Art Register Research, Allocation Lists, circa 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
    - Art Register Research, State Lists, circa 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Art Register Research, National Search, circa 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 8-10)
    - Report, Register of New Deal Art, circa 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Williams Collection Research, 1935-1999; 5.3
    Correspondence and research related to O'Connor's 1996 research project for print collectors Dave and Reba Williams. The subseries includes a copy of the final report co-written with Avis Berman, The Graphic Art Workshops of the WPA Federal Art Project, as well as research drafts, notes, and photocopies of original WPA source material.
    - Correspondence, circa 1983-1999 (Box 19, Folder 12-16)
    - Research, Drafts and Notes, circa 1968-1996; 3 Floppy discs (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Administrators, circa 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Artists, circa 1968-1995 (Box 19, Folder 21-22)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Correspondence, circa 1937-1993 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Economic Data and Sources, circa 1940-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Graphic Art, circa 1940-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Hearings, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - WPA/FAP Research, NY Employment Data, circa 1936-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - WPA/FAP Research, NY Projects, circa 1936-1967 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - WPA/FAP Research, NY Reports, circa 1939-1943 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - WPA/FAP Research, Reports, circa 1935 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Printed Material, 1963-2008; Series 6; 3.4 Linear feet Boxes 20-24
  Materials comprise of clippings, reports, press releases, and miscellaneous printed material that document the history of federal arts patronage in the United States after the New Deal. These materials were gathered by O'Connor as part of the preliminary research for an unwritten book project.
  Materials retain O'Connor's topical and chronological arrangements.
  - Government Art Patronage, Artists' Housing, circa 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Government Art Patronage, Artists' Rights, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Government Art Patronage, Associated Councils of the Arts, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Government Art Patronage, Grants to Artists, 1968-1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Government Art Patronage, Legislation, circa 1965-1970 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Government Art Patronage, Canada Arts Council, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Government Art Patronage, Maryland Arts Council, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Government Art Patronage, New York C.A.P.S. Project, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Government Art Patronage, New York State Council on Arts, circa 1968-1979 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
  - Government Art Patronage, State Arts Councils, circa 1968-1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1963-1969 (Box 20, Folder 19-23)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1970-1975 (Box 21, Folder 1-10)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 11-19)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1-10)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 11-20)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1986-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1-8)
  - Government Art Patronage, Chronological, 1992-2008 (Box 24, Folder 1-13)